devryu.net 2017-11-15

# Privacy Statement

Pearson Education Privacy Statement 

GENERAL INFORMATION ABOUT THE PRIVACY STATEMNT FOR PEARSON EDUCATION WEB SITES AND OTHER ONLINE RESOURCES 

Pearson Education Web sites are maintained by Pearson Education, Inc., One Lake Street, Upper Saddle River, New Jersey 07458. 

Pearson Education ("Pearson") recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of Personally Identifiable Information about you as a user of our online learning applications, websites and educational evaluation tools ("applications"). Follows is an overview of Pearson's Privacy Policy which is wholly contained within the [ Pearson End-User License and Privacy Agreement](https://register.pearsoncmg.com/reg/include/license2.jsp) to which end users consent when registering for a Pearson application. 

Information considered by Pearson to be Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") is: your full name, address, email address, username and password, phone number, and credit or debit card information. The name of the school you attend or your workplace, date of birth, personal interests, and grade information is also considered personally identifiable information when combined with PII. 

PII may be used by Pearson to facilitate subscription processing, validate access rights upon login and provide a personalized user experience, and help us improve our products. It will be treated confidentially within Pearson. 

Pearson policy is not to share PII with third parties without your consent except as expressly stated herein, however, we may share this information with Pearson affiliated companies for the purpose of supporting the application. 

Pearson may use PII to market (i.e. contact users for participation in focus groups, seminars, or product reviews, or provide information on complimentary or upgrade products) only to users ages 13 and above who have opted in to receive such information from Pearson. 

Pearson may disclose PII to third parties not affiliated with Pearson, in the following situations. 

  * Within application rosters, grade books, or communication tools that facilitate instructor and student engagement. 
  * Where disclosure is requested by the educational institution, school district or system in which the user is enrolled, or by applicable state educational authorities, for educational or administrative purposes. 
  * In the event of suspected illegal conduct, misappropriating password access, violating Pearson Terms of Use or engaging in academic misconduct or other conduct prohibited by an end-user’s academic institution or workplace. 

You should be aware that any PII voluntarily posted to a public area of a Pearson application (posting to a bulletin board or chat room) might be collected and used by others. Pearson cannot prevent such uses. 

SPECIAL NOTICE TO PARENTS: Pearson has no intention of seeking PII about minors (children under age 13). If obtained, Pearson’s privacy policies will apply to that information. In addition, if Pearson can identify a user as a minor, the PII will not be used for marketing and promotion. Pearson encourages you to ask your children to seek your permission before providing information about themselves or their family over the Internet. 

SPECIAL NOTICE TO CHILDREN: Ask your parent or guardian for permission before you sign up for any Website or send any personal information over the Internet, including through email. 

CONTACT INFORMATION: 

75 Arlington Street, Suite 300, Boston, MA 02116 

v9 - last updated 01 July 2010
